thebeaverton.com 2017-12-01

# Privacy Policy - The Beaverton

**The Beaverton Website Privacy Policy**

**1\. General**

BVT Digital Inc. (“BVT Digital”) respects your privacy and believes the best way to serve you on the Internet is with honesty, accountability and adherence to legal standards. We are sensitive to the issue of privacy and have structured our online activities to maximize your control over the disclosure of your own personally identifiable information. This Site is for information purposes only and the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy relate specifically to this Site and do not apply to websites operated by other third parties, which have their own terms of use and privacy policies. Please read the respective sites’ terms and policies when accessing those sites. This Privacy Policy Statement supplements our general Terms of Use, which you must also read. By using our website (the “Site”), you agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy and by the Terms of Use. We may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting revisions to the Site, and your continued use of the Site indicates your agreement to the revised terms. Accordingly, you should check the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy from time to time to keep informed of such amendments, and, if you do not agree to the terms of this or any revised policy, please exit the Site immediately.

**2\. Information**

**(a) What Information is collected?**

BVT Digital may collect personal identification information from users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when users visit our site, register on the site, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, username and/or an email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except where it prevents them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

We use MailChimp to manage our email list. There is no third-party tracking in messages we send through MailChimp besides MailChimp’s own analytics, which may aggregate how many subscribers open a message or click the links inside. MailChimp’s privacy policy is available at [http://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy](http://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy).

BVT Digital may transparently collect non-personal identifiable aggregate information through the use of cookies or by other means. (For more information about cookies, please click [here](https://www.thebeaverton.com/cookies-policy) or see Section 4 below.) Non-personal identification aggregate information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**(b) Why is the Information Collected?**

BVT Digital may collect your personal information in order to enable BVT Digital to make general improvements to the Site, ensure that content standards of the Site are rigorously upheld, enable us to contact you and better serve your specific interests. We may also request you to voluntarily provide personal information that is required to access features of our Site.

BVT Digital may transparently collect non-personally identifiable aggregate information through the use of cookies or by other means. We use this information to assess general usage patterns, including identifying repeat users, collect demographic information, administer and make improvements to the Site to tailor our visitors’ experiences at the Site and display content according to their preferences so as to make it more useful to you and other users. BVT Digital, and such other third party as we may designate reserve the right to use, maintain, update, disclose and/or sell Aggregate Information to third parties.

**(c) What We Will and Will** **Not** **Do With the Information You Provide**

BVT Digital uses information generally to compile statistical data, keep in contact with users, improve the content of our Site and provide them with a better interactive experience. BVT Digital may use your information specifically for the following purposes: (i) to run and operate our Site; (ii) to notify visitors about updates to our Site; (iii) to identify our visitors’ preferences; (iv) to keep you informed about products and services (both ours and third parties’) in which you have expressed an interest; (v) to run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature; (vi) to contact you as part of a promotion or contest of interest; (vii) to meet legal requirements; (viii) to provide Internet security; and/or (ix) to analyze the collected information to understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site and (x) to display content on the Site accurately. If you have entered and won one of BVT Digital’s contests, BVT Digital and / or its sponsors may publish your name and city of residence.

In the event that we sell a substantial portion of our business assets, our customer information may be among the transferred assets. In such event, the purchaser will inherit the confidentiality obligations posted herein.

Other than for the specific purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy Statement above in Section 2(c), we will not disclose your personal information to any third parties unless we obtain your prior consent or are legally compelled to do so. In addition, we will not contact you without your permission except as specified above or in connection with a registration process. On the Site, you will be given the opportunity to indicate whether you would like to receive e-mails, promotional and/or marketing information about other products, services and offerings from BVT Digital and/or any third parties or other information from BVT Digital. In the event you no longer wish to receive this information you can unsubscribe at any time. (To unsubscribe from future correspondence please use the unsubscribe link at the bottom of one of the newsletters.)

**How Secure is Your Information**

Any unauthorized use of the Site may result in criminal and/or civil prosecution. We have policies and procedures in place to protect the privacy and confidentiality of your information that we collect and maintain. All personal information is stored on secured servers, behind a firewall at a data centre with access to data strictly controlled. Only individuals specifically involved in the analysis and other functions set out herein have access to your personally identifiable information. These individuals have been provided the requisite training on our privacy policies and practices.

**3\. Third-Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable aggregated information we compile about your visits to this Site in order to provide advertisements on this Site about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Neither BVT Digital nor any third parties will make any attempt to link this anonymous aggregated traffic and other information to the individual visiting our Site. Except as otherwise detailed in this Privacy Policy, information that personally identifies you will be kept strictly confidential. Any third-party promotions and offers will only be made available through us on behalf of the third parties. 

**4.   Cookies**

When you visit the Site, a third-party advertiser or we may store or recognize some information on your computer in the form of a “cookie” or similar file. “Cookies” are small text files that identify an individual computer’s browser entering the Site. They do not pose a security threat to you. No personal information is stored within the cookies. For example, cookies allow us to track a browser’s movement through the Site over several sessions. Through cookies, the Site can recognize repeat visitors, facilitate the visitor’s access to and use of the Site and allows the Site to track usage behaviour that will allow content improvement and enable us to tailor our Site to better match your interests and preferences. If you do not want cookies placed on your computer, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Most Internet browsers or other software will allow you to do this. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions. If you reject cookies, functionality of the Site may be severely limited, and you may not be able to take advantage of many of the Site’s best features.

**5\. Onsite Notifications**

This Site uses Roost Web Push Notifications which allows us to send notifications to site visitors for updates about new posts. You may receive notifications for new updates to the site. Other message types may be considered for push notifications in the future. You can also control whether you receive these notifications. When you receive a push notification, your application’s icon and a message will appear in the status bar, at this point you will have the ability to either accept or block the notifications. The privacy policy of the service provider manages access, use and disclosure of your personal data that results from your use of these services. Learn how to [turn push notification on and off](https://goroost.com/blog/unsubscribe-from-chrome-notifications).

**6\. Linking to Third-Party Content / Websites**

The Site provides other third-party content. We are not responsible for any such third-party content or that you may access through the Site. The Site also contains links from and to sites operated by other independent third parties. Once you leave the Site, you may or may not see a new URL in the location bar. Please review the linked sites’ and third-party content providers’ privacy policies, and if you do not agree to be bound by the terms of the policies governing that provider / site, terminate your use of that service or your visit to the site. The linked sites are not under our influence or control, and we are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices or the content of the linked sites (which have their own terms of use and privacy policies) or contents of any subsequent links from that site.  
  
**7\. Termination**

Without limiting the foregoing, BVT Digital shall have the right to immediately terminate your access to this Site in the event of any conduct by you which we, in our sole discretion, consider to be unacceptable, or in the event of any breach by you of any of these Terms of Use and/or this Privacy Policy.  

**Questions / Concerns?**

If you have any concerns about privacy procedures at our Site:

**Email us at:**
